每个人都认同 一年中最重要的日子之一
Everyone would agree that one of the most important days of the year
就是母亲节
is Mother's Day.
母亲节快乐!
Happy Mother's Day!
噢 你们不用如此费心的
Oh, you guys didn't have to do this.
人人都想让妈妈知道自己有多爱她
Everybody wants to show their mama how much they love them.
就连痞子2Pac都写了首关于他老妈的歌 (歌名monther fuck -_-)
Even 2Pac wrote a song about his mother.
在母亲节那天 人们都各显神通
On Mother's Day, people pull out all the stops.
带母亲去吃早午餐...
You take your mother to brunch...
食物售罄
We're out of food.
我为所带来的不便表示抱歉
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
你们可以下周日再来
If you could just come back next Sunday.
你你你啥意思 食物售罄? 下周日?
What-What do you mean you're out of food? Next Sunday?
都没了啊 妈妈 你要我咋办
We're out of food, Mama. What you want me to do?
带她去看大片 这样她就可以带顶漂亮的大帽子..
We take her to a great movie so she can wear a great big hat...
为她花光最后1毛钱
and you spend your last dime on her,
让她知道她是家里最重要的一员
just so she knows she's number one.
噢 天那!
Oh, my God!
来吧
Come on.
噢 真不敢相信你送了这个
Oh, I can't believe you did this.
但如果是父亲节 没人会鸟他
But when it comes to Father's Day, nobody gave a damn.
父亲节到了 大家
It's Father's Day, people.
都来草原小岸吧
Come on down to Pastures and Shores.
食物五折优惠
The food is half-price.
晚上好
Buenas noches.
五折优惠哦!
Como se dice "half-off"?
电影也糟透了...
The movies are terrible...
关了它! 关了它!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
礼物也很烂...
...the gifts suck...
啥玩意啊这是?
What the hell is this?
泊车位 亲爱的
It's a parking space, honey.
我们送你个泊车位
We got you a parking space.
最好心满意足的收下泊车位吧
Better park and be happy.
为父亲们而做的歌只有这首
And the only song for fathers was this.
*老爸曾是颗滚石啊 *
* Papa was a rolling stone, *
*儿子哟 *
* my son, yeah *
今年 我想送我爸一份完美的礼物
This year, I wanted to get my father the perfect gift,
所以要问他想要什么
and the only way to do that was to ask him what he wanted.
爸爸 你父亲节想要什么礼物?
Dad, what present do you want for Father's Day?
你父亲节想要什么礼物?
You want to get me something for Father's Day?
帮我付份帐单吧
You can help me knock off one of these bills.
Julius...
好吧
Okay.
父亲节...
Father's Day...
知道吗?
You know what?
你们真的想在父亲节 送我礼物吗?
Y'all really want to get me something for Father's Day?
- 我知道我需要啥 - 是啥 宝贝?
- I know exactly what I want. - What's that, baby?
一天的休息
A day off.
你的意思是一天不去上班?
You mean a day off from work?
不是
No.
没有任何事和任何人打扰的一天
A day off from everything and everybody.
没有打打闹闹
No fighting,
没有瞎嚷嚷
no shouting,
没有喋喋不休
no complaining,
没有要修的
no fixing.
让我想干啥就干啥的一天
Just one day where I can do whatever I feel like doing.
我希望他不是想离开我们 和个白人小妞私奔
I hope he doesn't want to leave us for a white girl.
1x22 Everybody Hates Father's Day
Transcript: Raceman Syncrho: Sixe
人人都恨克里斯 第1季 第22集 "人人都恨父亲节"
等等 你爸爸说他啥也不要?
So, wait, your dad says he doesn't want anything?
也不是 他说他想要一个人待着
Nope. All he said was he wanted to be all alone.
你最好留个心眼儿
You better watch out.
我妈妈曾说过她想独自待一天
My mother said she wanted a day alone.
后来 她就跑路搬到Poughkeepsie去了
The next thing we knew, she left and moved to Poughkeepsie.
嗯 我不管他说了什么 我得为他做点什么
Well, I don't care what he says. I'm gonna get him something.
我爸爸讲了他要什么
My father said what he wanted.
最后他能得到什么我妈妈说了算
My mother said what he was gonna get.
脱离你家庭的一天 这算啥礼物?
What kind of gift is a day off from your family?
就只是一天而已啊
It's just one day.
好吧 那你能想象孩子们是啥感受?
Well, how is that supposed to make the kids feel?
女人总用孩子来折腾男人
Women always used the kids against you.
明明是父亲节 你想要的却是不当父亲
It's Father's Day and you don't want to be a father.
我没那么说啊
I did not say that.
他们想为你庆祝
They're trying to honor you,
你却说 "让我一个人待会"
and all you got to say is, "Leave me the hell alone."
我没说 "让我一个人待会"
I did not say, "Leave me the hell alone."
你说的差不多就是这个意思
You may as well have.
这13年来我都没自己的一天时间
I haven't had a day to myself in 13 years.
如果我不想做爸爸的话.. 我..
If I didn't want to be a father, I...
那表情的意思是 如果你还想做个父亲的话
That look means if you want to keep beg a father
你最好就的赶紧闭嘴
you better keep your mouth shut.
本来那天就该是让我们 为你做点啥特别的
It is supposed to be our day to do something special for you.
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm trying to say.
父亲节啊 我为啥就不能想咋样就咋样呢?
It's Father's Day. Why can't I do what the hell I want to do?
额? 你说啥呢?
Huh? Say what?
额... 你拿了钥匙吗?
Uh... you got the key?
你自己在这待一整天要干啥?
Well, what you gonna do here all day by yourself anyway?
啥也不做
Nothing.
那孩子们至少 可以给你份真正的礼物吧?
Well, can the kids at least get you a real gift?
怎么了?
What?
那是什么?
What's that?
过去4年里我收到的所有 父亲节的贺卡和礼物
Every Father's Day card and present I've gotten for the past four years.
看看这个
Look at this.
一盒直发剂
A box of S-Curl.
我送你的
I got you that.
通心粉做的烟盒
A macaroni cigar box.
- 真可爱 - 还有4条领带..
- That's so cute. - I got four ties--
领带 领结
a neck tie, a bow tie,
饰扣式领带...
bolo tie...
我送的这个
I got him that.
还有个夹子式领带
...and a clip-on tie.
我都不带领带的
I don't even wear ties.
我又不用出席什么重要场合
I don't go nowhere.
那28.46美圆可以有别的用途
That's $28.46 we could have used on something else.
重要的是我们的心意
Well, it's the thought that counts.
我很感激 真的
I appreciate it, I really do,
但是你买给我礼物
but if you buy me presents,
我就不得不去工作来买单
I'm just gonna have to work to pay it off.
这样的话
At this rate,
我死了也得继续工作
I'll be working when I'm dead.
Julius 你死了 你在这干吗?
Julius, you're dead. What are you doing here?
要付清那些礼物的钱啊
Trying to pay off these presents.
听着 我能在墓地找个活干吗?
Listen, can I work the graveyard shift?
好吧
Fine.
那好吧
Okay, then.
享受你的小破臭假期去吧
Have your little stinky day off.
但是我保证 在你生日那天
But on your birthday I will promise you this.
你会收到个蛋糕 也会喜欢的
You will be getting a cake, and you will like it.
我知道
I know.
你后退 自吻吧
You better jump back and kiss yourself.
还有 在你休息之前
And, uh, put up the groceries.
把这些杂货放好
Before your day off.
他有什么爱好吗?
Does he have any hobbies?
睡懒觉也算吗?
Is taking naps a hobby?
不算
No.
那你在父亲节那天要送什么给你爸爸?
So, what are you getting your dad for Father's Day?
我不知道"送"这个词是否合适
I don't know if "getting" is the right word.
更像是"做"
It's more like "doing."
好吧 那你会为你爸爸做些什么?
Okay, so what are you doing for your dad?
嗯 首先 我会为他做最喜欢的早餐
Well, first, I'm making his favorite breakfast--
谷物早餐跟哈密瓜
Cap'n Crunch and cantaloupe.
我试着想象为我爸做Greg所说的
I tried to imagine doing the things that Greg talked about with my father.
比如给他谷物早餐跟哈密瓜
Like bringing him Cap'n Crunch and cantaloupe.
你傻了吗?
Are you crazy?
儿子 你最好给俺弄点熏肉来
Boy, you better bring me some bacon.
我也想过带我爸爸去动物园看企鹅
I thought about taking my dad to the zoo to see some penguins.
我们花了3.50块就来看 这些不能飞的肥鸟?
We paid $3.50 to see a bird that can't fly?
接下来要我看什么 不吃奶酪的老鼠?
What you gonna show me next, rats that don't eat cheese?
还想了想在家门口放烟花火箭
I even imagined us shooting off bottle rockets in front of the house.
快跑 儿子 快跑!
Run, boy, run!
不知道Greg的爸爸有没中过弹
I wonder if Greg's dad ever got shot at.
你决定要做些什么了吗?
Have you decided what you're gonna do?
你讲的任何一件我都做不了
I can't do any of the stuff that you talked about.
我只有27块
I only have $27.
不错啊
That's not bad.
我要是你 就会搞清他想要啥 然后送给他就成了
If I were you, I'd try and figure out what he needs and just give him that.
要是我一掌扇掉他眉毛 会不会破坏我们的友谊呢
I wonder if it would ruin our friendship if I smacked his eyebrows off?
你找什么呢 Chris?
What you looking for, Chris?
我想找件父亲节礼物送我爸
I'm trying to find my father something for Father's Day.
父亲节
Father's Day.
我爸喜欢枪 酒 还有女人
My daddy liked guns, liquor and women.
我猜他还喜欢蹲牢子
I guess he liked jail, too.
你爸爸喜欢做什么?
What does your daddy like to do?
那可是个难题
That's the tough part.
他除了睡觉就是工作
All he does is sleep and work.
我能想象
I know what that's like.
但是我有样东西很合适
But I got just the thing.
一块瑞士石英表 有液晶屏 带计算跟闹铃功能
A Swiss LCD quartz calculator alarm watch.
嗯 家里他有个闹钟了
Well, he has an alarm clock at home.
他还要块带闹铃的表干吗?
What's he need one in his watch for?
以防万一啊
You never know.
幸好有这块表
Thank goodness for this watch.
我还真没这么想过
I never thought of that.
还带有计算功能
It's got a calculator, too.
他可以算出任何东西的价格
He can figure out how much anything costs.
要是再附上一条熏肉
If it came with a side of bacon,
这将是史上最完美的礼物了
that would have been the best gift in history.
这个多少钱?
How much does it cost?
24.95刀
$24.95.
他胡扯出来的价
He just made that up.
我买了
I'll take it.
妈妈 为什么爸爸不想和我们一起过父亲节?
Mama, how come Daddy doesn't want to be with us on Father's Day?
宝贝 不是你爸爸不想和我们一起
Oh, baby, it's not that your daddy doesn't want to be with us,
只是他平日工作太忙了
it's just that he works hard all the time
他只是想有自己的一点点时间
and he just wants to have a little time to be by himself.
真不错
Man, that's cool.
我都等不急自己当爸爸 这样我自己就可以拥有整个房子
I can't wait until I'm a father so I can have this whole house to myself.
你不会成为这房子里的父亲
You are not gonna be a father in this house,
因为我不可想再照顾任何婴儿
because I ain't taking care of no babies.
神经
Lost your mind.
我们可以送他礼物吗?
Well, can we still get him a present?
当然可以 宝贝 你有打算了?
Sure, baby. What'd you have in mind?
这个
These.
看 我把这些通心粉装饰到爸的旧拖鞋上了
See, I took daddy's old slippers and put macaroni on them.
噢 宝贝 真漂亮
Oh, baby, that's nice.
待会我会帮你包起来
I'm gonna help you wrap them later.
你也能帮我包礼物吗?
Can you help me wrap mine, too?
我在给爸爸做古龙水
I'm making dad cologne.
喔 你从哪里学来的做古龙水?
Oh, where did you learn how to make cologne?
从杂志背面看来的
I saw it in the back of a magazine.
我所需要的就是香油
All I need is oil,
一些香料 还有酒精
something to give it a little smell and, uh, alcohol.
然后放瓶子里闷个一周
Then just leave it in a jar for a week.
妈妈 既然爸爸想一个人过
Mama, since Daddy wants to be by himself,
那我们咋办?
what are we gonna do?
我们会找点乐子的
We are gonna have some fun.
Chris! 吃饭了!
Chris! Time to eat!
嗨 爸爸 那些都是什么东西?
Hey, Dad, what's all that stuff?
我那条线路上的朋友 送我的一包父亲节礼物
It's a bunch of stuff guys on my route got me for Father's Day.
喔 看看这个
Oh, look at this.
一块瑞士石英表 有液晶屏 带计算跟闹铃功能
It's an LCD quartz calculator alarm watch.
这是我得到的最好的礼物
It's the best gift I ever got.
也许我该在他鞋子上粘点通心粉
Maybe I could glue some macaroni to his shoes.
父亲节快乐!
Happy Father's Day!
父亲节快乐 宝贝
Happy Father's Day, baby.
我们爱你
We love you.
我也爱你们
I love y'all, too. Yeah.
你们今天会过的挺愉快 是吧?
Hey, y'all have fun today, okay?
爸爸 你不想先读读贺卡吗?
Daddy, aren't you gonna read your card?
噢 我看看
Ooh, yeah. Let's see here.
"献给世界上最好的老爸"
"To the Best Dad in the Whole World."
真体贴啊
That's so sweet.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
嘿 你们今天自己玩的开心点哈 拜拜
Hey, y'all enjoy y'all selves today, all right? Okay, bye-bye.
爸爸 我们早饭做了你最喜欢吃的东西
Dad, we made your favorite thing for breakfast.
还给你带了你的痛风药
And I brought your gout pills,
所以你现在吃啥都不用担心了
so now you can eat all you want without worrying.
熏肉 芝士蛋
Man, bacon, eggs with cheese,
饼干和黄油
biscuits and butter.
感觉像上了天堂一样
I feel like I died and went to heaven.
- 谢谢 宝贝 - 没什么 宝贝
- Thank you, baby. - Oh, ain't nothing, baby.
- 这都是孩子们做的 - 你们啥时候走 嗯?
- They did it all. - When y'all leaving, huh?
好吧 马上走
All right, in a minute.
不客气
And you're welcome.
还有宝贝 记得要吃这些药 好吗?
And baby, make sure you take those pills, okay?
好的
All right.
你们几个准备好 我们得走了
You guys go get ready so we can go.
快点 迅速点
Hurry up, now. Hurry up. Faster.
- 他们是不是很体贴? - 走吧
- Isn't that sweet? - There you go.
我们有世上最好的孩子
We have the best kids in the world.
- 是啊 - 他们体贴
- Oh, yeah. - They're so sweet.
是的
They are.
那表情是 "你怎么还赖着不走?"
That look means, "Ain't you supposed to be leaving?"
你也得快点 我的意思是...
You better hurry up. I mean...
你快要迟到了 额..嗯..
You're gonna be late for your, uh, the, um...
额..
Uh, the...
额 你们要去干吗?
Uh, what y'all doing?
先去趟博物馆
We're going to the museum.
然后去看电影
And to see the movie Trading Places.
- 噢 那一定非常有趣 - 是的 是的
- Oh, that should be funny. - Right. Right.
那你最好快点啦
So, you better hurry up, all right?
好了 Julius 我们走了
Okay, Julius, we're leaving.
晚饭时我会回来的 好吧?
All right, well, I'll be home in time for dinner, okay?
谢谢 我爱你
Thank you. I love you.
我也爱你 宝贝
I love you, too, baby.
祝你过的愉快
You have a good day.
嗯 我会的
All right. Oh, I will.
赶快出去吧
Get on out of here.
父亲节快乐!
Happy Father's Day!
- 你玩得开心点 - 我会的
- Hey, enjoy yourself. - I will.
对我爸来说 可以过上随心所欲的一天
For my father to have one day where he could do
就像找到百万美元似的
whatever he felt like doing was like finding a million dollars.
他在沙发上睡觉
He slept on the couch.
他在床上睡
He slept in the bed.
他在饭桌睡 做他的白日大美梦
He slept on the dining room table and dreamt his favorite dreams.
17分钱的黄油
17 cent worth of butter.
他看保龄球
He watched bowling.
耶!
Yeah!
棒!
Yes!
他看棒球
He watched baseball.
- 投球 接着... - 耶!
- Here's the pitch. And... - Yeah!
他看高尔夫
He watched golf.
球在路上 进了
It's on it way, and it's in.
甚至做了我们都不知道他会的事 比如画画
He even did stuff we didn't know he did, like painting.
还有唱他最爱的歌曲
And singing his favorite songs.
一开始我很担心 不知所措
一直在想 ]有你在身边 我一定活不下去
但是后来 我花了很多个夜晚
思考你是如何错待我
我开始变的坚强 学会了独立
你从火星
回到地球
I didn't say he knew all the words.
我可没说他记得住词
我走进屋 看见你满脸凄楚
我早该换个门锁
我早该叫你把钥匙留下
如果我知道
你会回来骚扰我的话
噢 走吧!
滚回火星吧
转身滚蛋吧
你一点也不受欢迎
你不正是那个抛弃我的负心汉
你觉得我会崩溃?
就这样郁郁而终?
我不是这种人!
我会活下去~
当我爸爸在做平时我们在的时候 他不会做的事
While my father was doing things he wouldn't do while we were around,
我们也在做平时他在的时候 我们不会做的事
we were doing things we wouldn't do while he was around.
你们都要待在我视线范围内
Okay, y'all stay where I can see you.
好吧 Chris 你确定吗?
All right, now, Chris, you sure about this?
Harris先生把表钱退给我了
Mr. Harris gave me my money back on the watch,
所以我想去买东西
so I wanted to go shopping
看看能不能找到爸爸喜欢的东西
and see if I can find Dad something that he'll like.
行 不过不管有没买到礼物
Okay. But gift or no gift,
你要是6点半不回家 我就叫警察
if you're not home by 6:30, I'm calling the police.
我妈妈经常告诫我们 要是不按时回家
My mother always told us if we weren't home on time,
她就会叫警察
she was calling the police.
给你
Here.
这是什么?
What's this?
这钱本来用来给你爸爸买礼物的
Oh, it's just money I was gonna use to buy a gift for your dad.
谢谢
Thanks.
别客气 宝贝 小心点
You're welcome, baby. Be careful.
唯一比给拥有一切的人
The only thing tougher than finding a gift
买个礼物还难的事
for the man that has everything
就是给个啥也不要的人买礼物
is finding one for the man that wants nothing.
我爸穿西装 只会是在葬礼 毕业典礼上
The only time my father wore a suit was at funerals, graduations,
以及洗衣日那天
and on laundry day.
我爸爸最近的一次接近珠宝
The closest my father got to jewelry
是听Neil Diamond(钻石)的歌
was listening to Neil Diamond.
希望钻石能跟分期一样恒久远
I hope it lasts as long as the payments.
我不确定他会去喂兔子 还是用兔子来喂我们
I wasn't sure if he would feed the rabbit, or use the rabbit to feed us.
很明显他也不是穿腿套的料
And let's just say he wasn't the leg warmer type.
当我试着想出该给父亲买点啥的时候
While I was trying to figure out what to get my father,
我妈妈在想她给自己揽了什么蠢差事
my mother was trying to figure out what she had gotten herself into.
那是什么?
What is that?
呃宝贝
Well, honey,
那是艺术
that's art.
你确定?
You sure?
看起来像是有人中枪后掉进芥末桶里去了
Looks like somebody got shot and fell in a bucket of mustard.
安静 儿子
Be quiet, boy.
这是文化
This is culture.
那我们还要吸收多少文化?
How much more culture do we have to get?
女儿 就盯着这画看
Girl, just look at the picture.
我希望爸爸在这里
I wish Dad was here.
也许他能解释这个
Maybe he could explain this.
- 嘿 Risky? - 等等 小子
- Hey, Risky? - Hold up, little man.
我把想得到的地方都找了个遍
I had looked for a gift everywhere I could,
最后决定来不该来的地方找找
so I decided to look somewhere I shouldn't look.
你有什么样的父亲节礼物?
So, what kind of stuff do you have for Father's Day?
父亲节?
Father's Day?
这对我来说不是啥大事
That ain't a big one for me.
你知道这附近就只有4个爸爸
You know there ain't none but four fathers in the neighborhood.
要是母亲节 我可有一大箩筐东东
Now, Mother's Day-- I had a whole bunch of stuff.
小子 你有多少钱可花?
Man, how much you got to spend?
37块
$37.
37块? 你干啥了 劫了家酒店??
$37? What you do, knock over a liquor store?
我存下来的
I saved up.
继续这么存
Man, you keep saving up like that,
你很快就是个富翁了
you'll be rich in a minute.
也许那时我会买件 他穿的这种粉色毛衣
Maybe then I can buy one of those pink sweaters, like him.
你爸爸听音乐吗?
Your old man like music?
有谁的?
Who's that?
我们有约翰・特拉沃塔
We got John Travolta,
威廉・夏特纳
William Shatner.
李柏瑞斯
Liberace.
这是给听不了 艾尔顿・约翰的年长父亲们的
That's for fathers that were too old for Elton John.
不 谢谢了
No, thanks.
你还有些别的吗?
What else you got?
这些怎样... 送你老妈?
How about these... for your mom?
- 以父亲节的名义? - 嗯 给你爸送给你妈
- For Father's Day? - Yeah. For him to give to her.
不
No.
抱歉我不能帮你了 小屁孩
I'm sorry I can't help you out, young blood,
但是母亲节那天来找我 保证让你满意
but, hey, you come back Mother's Day-- I'll hook you up.
听着 帮我看着这里几分钟好吗?
Listen, why don't you watch this for a few minutes?
我要过街付电费
I'm gonna run across the street, pay my light bill.
- 好吗? - 好的
- All right? - Sure.
告诉你爸爸打电话给我 顺便祝他父亲节快乐
Tell your daddy to call me and happy Father's Day.
回到家 我爸爸仍然独自一人霸着大屋
Back at home, my father still had the house to himself...
Rochelle?
Chris?
不管他喜欢与否
...whether he liked it or not.
And if you order now, you'll get a set of microwavable...
In the city that never sleeps.
Psychic Station TV Network...
这个骄傲的公鹅也不例外
This proud father goose is no exception.
他和蔼的关注着 保护着他的小孩
He graciously watches over and protects his chicks,
在它们能自己独立自保之前 保护着他们的安全
assuring their safety until they are old enough to fend for themselves.
在野外 小动物不会被父母抛弃
In the wild, babies are almost never abandoned,
父母也不会长时间留他们独处
and rarely left alone for any extended period of time.
一代伟人曾说过
A great man once said,
"大爱无言 大言无声"
"Nothing screams louder than the sound of silence."
我想这是绿野仙踪里的铁皮人说的
I think it was Nipsy Russell.
谢谢 祝你看得开心
Thank you. Enjoy your show.
嗨  我要一张成人票
Hi. Um, can I have one adult,
二张儿童票 看
two children for Trading Places, please?
你一定当我傻呢
You must think I'm a fool.
你想要我相信他不到12岁?
You want me to believe he's under 12?
他就是不到啊
Yeah, she does.
- 嗨! - 爸爸!
- Hey! - Dad!
你在这干吗 宝贝?
What are you doing here, baby?
我想你们啊
I missed you guys.
没有家人陪伴的父亲节
Father's Day without your family--
感觉像我不是个父亲似的
it's like not being a father.
那表情是说
That look means,
"我一直跟你这么说啊 笨蛋!"
"That's what I was trying to tell yo' stupid ass!"
来吧
Come here.
- Chris呢? - 噢 他去给你买礼物了
- Where's Chris? - Oh, he went to buy you a gift.
- 但是我都说了... - Julius 拜托
- But I told... - Julius, please,
答应我 你就表现的像是你从没收到过 这么好的礼物似的 好吗?
just promise me you will act like it's the best gift you've ever gotten, okay?
我答应
I promise.
好吧 好吧
All right. All right.
2个孩子 2个大人 看
That'll be two kids, two adults for, uh, Trading Places.
- 这是啥? - 父亲节特惠 一票两人用
- What's this? - Father's Day special-- two for one.
父亲节快乐 爸爸
Happy Father's Day, Daddy.
我做了这个送你
I made these for you.
我知道你说不要送礼物的
I know you said, don't get you a gift,
但是我还是想送你点什么 怕你又改变主意啥的
but I wanted to give you something just in case you changed your mind.
噢! 通心粉装饰的拖鞋!
Oh! Macaroni-covered slippers!
和去年送的通心粉烟盒正好凑一对
It goes with the macaroni-covered cigar box I got last year.
我知道
I know.
嗨 爸爸 我也有东西送你
Hey, Dad, I got something for you, too.
哦 这是什么?
Oh, what's this?
一瓶碘酒?
A bottle of iodine?
不不 这是古龙水 我亲手做的
No, no, no, it's cologne. I made it myself.
只是一时找不到瓶子装
I just couldn't find a bottle to put it in,
就把碘酒给倒了 然后装了这瓶子里
so I poured the iodine out and put it in there.
儿子 那碘酒值99...
Boy, that iodine cost 99...
闻起来不错
That smells good.
谢谢你 Drew
Thank you, Drew.
非常感谢你
Oh, man, thank you so much.
你知道我正要去报警吗?
You know I was about to call the police, right?
嘿 Chris你去哪里了?
Hey, Chris, where you been?
我试着给你找份父亲节礼物
I was trying to find you a gift for Father's Day.
嗯 无论你带来了什么 都不错
Well, I'm sure whatever you got, it's-it's fine.
事实上 我寻遍了各处
That's the thing-- I looked all over,
都没找到我觉得你会喜欢的东西
but I couldn't find you anything that I thought you would like.
没关系 Chris 重要的是你的心意
Doesn't matter, Chris. I mean, it's the thought that counts.
那你找到了吗?
So, did you find something?
没有
Not really.
但我为你做了点东西
It's more of, I did something for you.
什么?
What?
这是什么?
What is it?
一个收据
It's a receipt.
他交了电费
He paid the electric bill.
噢 宝贝 这真是..
Oh, baby, that is so...
当我问你 送什么父亲节礼物的时候
When I asked you if I could get you anything
你说我可以帮你清张帐单
for Father's Day, you said I could help you knock out a bill.
电费是我唯一可以付得起的
That was the only one I could afford.
谢谢 儿子
Thanks, son.
我爸爸从不真的在乎啥礼物
My father never really cared much about presents,
但是给他个微笑的理由 是我为他做的最好的事
but giving him a reason to smile was the best thing I could ever do for him.
这是我收到的最棒的礼物
This is the best gift I ever got.
我会永远记住这个的
I'll remember this forever.
父亲节快乐
Happy Father's Day.
我以你为荣 Chris
I'm proud of you, Chris.
每天越来越像个大人了
Becoming more of a man every day.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你知道吗 我在想
You know, I was thinking,
你找份工作 然后每个月都付点帐单 会是个不错的主意
it might be a good idea if you get a job and start paying a bill every month.